With supplies being limited,
we'll need to add a rule allowing
passage in and out of the Colony.
But I can't afford to
let Players like Dhruv,
who attack people indiscriminately,
to leave the barriers.
So that will have to come after
eliminating all Players like him
from the other Colonies, too.
So communication between
Colonies is a necessity.
1: Transfer Points
2: Escape From
the Culling Game
3: Passage In and
Out of Colonies
4: Communication In
and Out of Colonies
So there are the two rules
Fushiguro-kun proposed:
a means of communication,
and passage in and out of the Colonies.
That means we'll need four additional
rules to get this situation under control.
Everyone's worn out from Shibuya, too.
They're at their limit,
physically and emotionally.
Sensei...
I won't let you kill
your best friend twice.
I'll be the one to kill Kenjaku.
I'll obtain 400 points on my own.
JUJUTSU KAISEN
It's okay to come out now.
Let's continue making our way
north to the edge of the barrier.
Carry me.
Hang in there, okay?
Let's take a short break.
This stadium was controlled by the
powerful sorcerer I just defeated.
People will be hesitant to
approach it for a while yet.
What's that sound?!
Run into the stadium.
Hurry.
H-Help!
Are these cockroaches real?!
Damn it!
Rika! Knock it down!
Hurry!
Okay!
Kogane, is that a Player?
Yeah. It's called Kurourushi.
So some Players are cursed spirits, too?
Episode 59
Sendai Colony
Festering Life Sword
I'm being watched.
Likely by the other two
Players with high points.
Why do you interfere?
Kurourushi is a cursed spirit.
Why do you kill us?
I can exorcise it for certain
if I drive positive energy from my
reverse cursed technique into its body.
That's what I'd like to know.
However...
I like the taste of iron!
I don't want those other two to know
I can use the reverse cursed technique.
And Rika is protecting
everyone in the stadium.
I want to exorcise Kurourushi without
using Rika or my reverse cursed technique.
Blinding, blinding, blinding...
You have earned five points.
I see you can use...
reverse cursed technique.
What was that?
A strike?
My arm is back to normal.
Nothing's off.
Her technique probably manipulates space.
But I guess it can't crush her
opponent along with said space.
It feels like it's creating errors similar
to the distortions from a lens.
My technique treats the
"sky" as a "surface."
Like this.
She's revealing her technique!
Hurry up and attack.
I'll go ahead and ask...
You're someone who won't complain
about getting killed, right?
I can understand powerless people
getting desperate for points,
but a strong person like you can
claim points whenever they want.
So what's your reason for
actively seeking a fight?
This little...
What, are sorcerers of this age
that casual about incarnation?
To us, this means coming
back from the dead!
People who lived out
their lives without regrets
wouldn't accept Kenjaku's
offer, would they?
He pisses me off.
The Culling Game is just the first step
toward a chance at a second life.
Keep in mind, Kenjaku
set the stage for this.
We should be earning points to prepare
for anything that could happen.
Do you not have any friends or lovers?
Huh?
I didn't have any friends
until recently either,
but I can't empathize with that.
Yeah. This feeling.
It's like he's tracing my trigger.
Even if you had regrets,
you're killing people hundreds—
thousands—of years removed from then.
How can you be so desperate
for your own sake?
Are you... one of the Fujiwara?!
What would anyone from your
bloodline understand?!
Granite Blast.
Ishigori?
That rooftop?
He's rather close.
Even with Rika protecting
the people in the stadium,
a direct hit from an attack on that
level would cause several to die.
So first, I'll take Ishigori...
Now that Kurourushi and Dhruv are gone,
I have no reason to let Ishigori run free.
I'll take both him and Okkotsu...
...out!
Granite Blast!
Come on, don't disappoint me.
He's gone?
Right! That's where Okkotsu
dug a hole earlier!
Please fight a little more discreetly.
Will that sate the hunger, Okkotsu?
JUJUTSU KAISEN
Would you tell a kid with
a feast before him
to slow down and take his time eating?
Wouldn't anyone?
Right. Most probably would.
That was a bad example.
My first run at life was
moderately filling.
I fought some guys with real backbone.
I met a nice woman, too.
Frankly, it would be hard
to say I had any regrets.
This vague hunger is the most
annoying kind, Okkotsu.
Everyone looks at me with
"What are you unsatisfied about?"
on their face.
Did you know these cigarettes have
a slightly sweet aftertaste?
There was no dessert in my life.
Here it comes!
Why am I unsatisfied?!
I think you know!
I'm unsatisfied because
I'm not fulfilled!
You'd better not be crushed!
Whoa.
That hurt.
Good.
Not calling your shikigami?
I can't.
Not with you going wild.
That's a shame.
He's probably trying to limit my paths,
but I'll break through...
head-on!
Sweet!
That's it, Okkotsu!
In that case...
His cursed energy is more precise!
This is bad!
Well done! Here's a reward!
Whoops.
I overheated.
You're good, Okkotsu!
Are you my dessert?!
You are the best!
What I strike isn't the person,
but the surface of the "sky."
Thin Ice Breaker!
Out of our way, you pile of vomit!
Can it, dick cheese!
You're resilient.
That's fine.
I decided to torment you anyway.
That packed a punch.
That's my first time
eating my own technique.
Reverse cursed technique
is a pain to deal with,
but it burns cursed energy like crazy.
We're finally seeing the bottom
of your reserves, Okkotsu.
No matter how delicious
or high-end the shop is,
seeing the displays empty
close to closing time
is always disappointing.
I guess it wasn't you.
I wanted to gain more distance
from everyone in the stadium.
Oh, well.
Come here, Rika.
Give me everything.
His shikigami completely manifested?!
How does that work?
He's swelling with
cursed energy again, too!
Yuta, which would you like?
Thank you.
I'll take that one.
"Rika" is the stockpile of cursed energy
and the externalization
of Okkotsu's technique
that remained with him after
Rika Orimoto passed on.
While connected to "Rika"
through the ring,
he gains the following:
use of his cursed technique,
the complete manifestation of "Rika,"
and cursed energy supplied by "Rika."
He can remain connected for five minutes.
Okay.
Let's go.
Don't underestimate me!
Don't move.
Don't Move
Snake eyes and fangs!
I can't move!
Hey, now.
You're super sweet, aren't you?!
Rika!
Aye!
Bring it!
It's tough!
That was close!
Don't act like you've won!
You!
I won't forgive you!
What?
Let's go!
Hell yeah!
Even with this, I can't fully block it!
Want a go?
Thin Ice Breaker!
Tsk!
The Sun, Moon, and Stars Squad was
the Fujiwara Clan's personal squad of assassins.
We lived in darkness and served with selfless devotion.
We were even forbidden from having our own names.
Yet that man once granted me a name.
So he could execute me instead
for his crime of slaying his own kin.
Fujiwara!
I've still got a strong appetite!
Let's keep chowing down!
It's always you, Fujiwara!
You always get in my way!
Are you that afraid of me?!
Afraid of me becoming my own person?!
Okkotsu had defeated Dhruv Lakdawalla,
whose technique made the path of
his shikigami into his domain,
which cut into anything it touched.
This is... Dhruv's technique!
Is Okkotsu's technique...
Copy?!
I don't know what my
ancestors did to you,
but you'll eventually reach your limit
if you live solely for yourself.
Shut up!
"Live for the sake of others!"
"There's no need to be your own person!"
It's always the ones who already became
someone who bark things like that!
Quit your annoying whining!
At this point...
words are unnecessary!
Domain Expansion!
Domain Expansion.
Give me back Yuta!
Even if it tries to penetrate
the barrier later...
I'm not going to drag this out!
Let's settle this nice and sweet!
At that moment, the black
devil of the modern age...
I like the taste of iron!
...flew into the barriers.
Kurourushi had completed parthenogenesis
before going dormant.
So Kurourushi was still alive
and well as a cursed spirit.
The complex forces of three domains
had been keeping them all in check.
But this intruder was unexpected.
And so the barriers
collapsed.
How is Kurourushi alive?!
Damn it!
I can't use my technique right
after Domain Expansion!
How dare you take my arm?!
Fujiwara!
That's enough, Uro.
You two aren't invited to this table.
Granite Blast.
Ishigori's technique is
Cursed Energy Discharge.
It's an extremely simple attack,
but it performs just as well
even when his technique is burnt out.
Now,
have a seat at our table,
Okkotsu.
Let's go, Rika.
Okkotsu can discharge a high
volume of cursed energy
only while Rika is completely manifested.
However, his maximum output is
slightly inferior to Ishigori's.
So he planned to charge and
unleash his cursed energy
before Ishigori reached maximum output.
At first.
Let's let it all out!
Four hundred years of longing.
The intense gaze full of that hunger
melted Yuta Okkotsu's heart,
even though he would likely
never find meaning in fighting.
Just this once.
That was seriously sweet, Okkotsu!
That's right!
Let's keep going!
That big thing can fire it on its own?!
But...
its force is weak!
After Domain Expansion
and a meal with me,
even you couldn't have
recovered that much.
I'll settle this.
Granite Blast!
Okkotsu's technique
had already recovered.
Uro's technique?!
I thought he was more than
just a cursed speech user!
I figured that big thing probably had
a different technique from Okkotsu's,
but I was wrong!
Okkotsu's technique is Copy!
But there should be strenuous
conditions on it!
When?! When did he
satisfy those conditions?!
While I wasn't looking?!
Don't tell me there are no conditions?!
That was when he did it!
Thin Ice Breaker!
Five minutes.
Okkotsu's connection
to "Rika" was severed.
Yuta!
I had no idea...
there was more after
wringing everything out!
This is what dessert is like!
Now we're done.
What?!
What is he after?!
Was this mine?
In that instant...
he sent it sailing back to
me using Uro's technique?
Thank you.
I'm full.
You're too soft, Okkotsu.
I'm not praising you.
Sparing the life of a sorcerer
who fought to kill you...
There's nothing to gain from it.
Uro-san told me the same thing.
That woman's still alive?
Well, I guess my blast was weaker
after my Domain Expansion.
She kept going on about something.
Were you having a lover's spat?
Something like that.
Don't look so annoyed by it.
There's nothing I can say to that woman.
Anything I say will lead to violence.
Because I'm blessed.
Is that how it works?
I don't get it.
Regardless,
please give me your points.
Now I get it.
You would have killed us
if not for this, right?
I'm not so sure.
You should be grateful to my friends.
Through the transfer of Ryu Ishigori
and Takako Uro's points,
Yuta Okkotsu came to possess 190 points.
You're the one who will
reach their limit.
I've seen it.
Be it sorcerer or cursed spirit,
those who surpass the
bounds of being strong
all have overwhelming egos.
They don't concern themselves
with other things.
They're calamities.
To Be Continued